Mayday is a thriller, tv movie film directed by T.J. Scott.
Twelve miles above the Pacific Ocean, an errant missile
strikes a state of the art passenger jet.
The flight crew is crippled or dead.
Now, defying both nature and man, a handful of survivors must
achieve the impossible: Land the airplane.
John Berry, played by Aidan Quinn.
Commander James Slan, played by Dean Cain.
Anne Metz, played by Gail O'Grady.
Admiral Randolf Hennings, played by Charles S. Dutton.
Linda Farley, played by Tamara Hope.
Captain Randall Williams, played by Michael Murphy.
Mayday is a 2005 American television thriller film based on
the 1979 novel by American author Thomas Block.
The novel was updated in 1998 by authors Thomas Block and
Nelson DeMille and re-released as a paperback.
The film was directed by T.
Scott and stars Aidan Quinn, Dean Cain, Kelly Hu, Michael Murphy, Charles S.
Dutton and Gail O'Grady.
It aired on CBS in the United States on October 2, 2005.
The tone is intense.